FOLAKEMI ADEYEYE

Phone: (+234)9075905604 Email: folakemiadeyeye3@,gmail.com

PERSONAL DATA

Nationality: Nigerian
Marital Status Single
Dob: 28/02/1995

PROFILE

Detail-oriented, efficient and organized professional with extensive experience in accounting systems. A solid multi-tasker with great hierarchical capacities, combined with a critical universal presentation prompting an elevated level of information in cross-culture and interdisciplinary approach.

Technical Skills: Microsoft Office Suite

CORE COMPETENCIES

 Analytical Skills 	 Adaptability &flexibility 	 Problem Resolution Skills
 Customer Service Orientation 	 Management Skills 	 Adaptive Team Player
 Research Skills 	 Competitive Intelligence 	 Communication Skills
 Account Management 	 High level of Integrity 	 Good Interpersonal Skills
	•	

EDUCATION DETAILS		
University of Ibadan School of Business		
• Masters in Business Administration (MBA)	2021	
Tolumi the fashion people (TFP)		
Diploma in fashion	2020	
Bowen University, Iwo, Osun State		
B Sc. (Hons.) Accounting (Second Class Lower)	2015	
Baptist Model High School, Ijegun	2011	
• West African Senior School Certificate Examination (WASSCE)		
Ultra International School, Ijegun	2004	
First School Leaving Certificate		
WARY EVERYENCE		

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fashion Intern Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

House of Habbybah

- Order supplies and research trends and current fashions, buy fabrics and pull together accessories to complement created pieces.
- Assist with fabric cutting and sewing, pattern making and setting up the show room.

• Plan for upcoming sales, events and product launches for clothing.

Sales Team Lead Dec 2018 - May 2019

Dashaka Green Village

- Mobilize workers in charge of marketing and sales for the distribution of the company's product
- Keep records of the inflow and outflow of cash Stock keeping
- Assist managers in sales strategy development
- Communicate deadlines and sales goals to team members
- Develop strategies to promote team member adherence to company regulations and performance goals

Accountant May 2014- June 2014

Seg Mashen Company.

- Input receipt of payment of work done into Peachtree
- Provides financial information to management by researching and analyzing accounting data; preparing reports
- Make sure auditor's signature is on all invoice before disbursement of cash
- Prepares Asset, liability and capital account entries by compiling and analyzing account information

Okobo Comprehensive School

Nov 2016-Oct 2017

Account Teacher

- Create an environment oriented to trust, open communications, creative thinking and cohesive team effort
- Draft lesson note ahead of the week and present to the principal for evaluation and review
- Teach courses in business administration and management, such as accounting, finance, human resources, marketing and operations research

Referees

Excellent Referees Available Upon Request